[
  
  {
    "id": 1,
    "topic": "GCF",
    "question": "Factor: 6x^2 + 9x",
    "choices": ["3x(2x+3)", "6x(x+3)", "9x(2x+1)", "3(x+3)"],
    "answer": "3x(2x+3)"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "topic": "GCF",
    "question": "Factor: 8x^3 + 4x^2",
    "choices": ["4x^2(2x+1)", "8x^2(x+1)", "2x(4x+2)", "4x(x^2+1)"],
    "answer": "4x^2(2x+1)"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "topic": "GCF",
    "question": "Factor: 12y^2 - 6y",
    "choices": ["6y(2y-1)", "12y(y-1)", "3y(4y-2)", "6(y-1)"],
    "answer": "6y(2y-1)"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "topic": "GCF",
    "question": "Factor: 10a + 20",
    "choices": ["10(a+2)", "20(a+1)", "5(2a+4)", "10a(1+2)"],
    "answer": "10(a+2)"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "topic": "GCF",
    "question": "Factor: 14x^2y + 21xy",
    "choices": ["7xy(2x+3)", "14xy(x+3)", "7x(2xy+3y)", "21xy(x+1)"],
    "answer": "7xy(2x+3)"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "topic": "GCF",
    "question": "Factor: 18m^2n - 6mn",
    "choices": ["6mn(3m-1)", "3mn(6m-2)", "6m(3mn-n)", "18mn(m-1)"],
    "answer": "6mn(3m-1)"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "topic": "GCF",
    "question": "Factor: 15x^3 + 5x^2",
    "choices": ["5x^2(3x+1)", "15x^2(x+1)", "5x(3x^2+1)", "x^2(15x+5)"],
    "answer": "5x^2(3x+1)"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "topic": "GCF",
    "question": "Factor: 9p^2 - 3p",
    "choices": ["3p(3p-1)", "9p(p-1)", "3(p^2-p)", "p(9p-3)"],
    "answer": "3p(3p-1)"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "topic": "GCF",
    "question": "Factor: 16x + 24",
    "choices": ["8(2x+3)", "16(x+3)", "4(4x+6)", "2(8x+12)"],
    "answer": "8(2x+3)"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "topic": "GCF",
    "question": "Factor: 21y^3 + 14y^2",
    "choices": ["7y^2(3y+2)", "21y^2(y+2)", "14y(y^2+1)", "7y(3y^2+2)"],
    "answer": "7y^2(3y+2)"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "topic": "GCF",
    "question": "Factor: 25x^2 - 5x",
    "choices": ["5x(5x-1)", "25x(x-1)", "5(x^2-x)", "x(25x-5)"],
    "answer": "5x(5x-1)"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "topic": "GCF",
    "question": "Factor: 30a^2b + 10ab",
    "choices": ["10ab(3a+1)", "30ab(a+1)", "10a(3ab+b)", "5ab(6a+2)"],
    "answer": "10ab(3a+1)"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "topic": "GCF",
    "question": "Factor: 4x^4 - 12x^3",
    "choices": ["4x^3(x-3)", "12x^3(x-1)", "4x(x^3-3x^2)", "x^3(4x-12)"],
    "answer": "4x^3(x-3)"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "topic": "GCF",
    "question": "Factor: 27m + 9",
    "choices": ["9(3m+1)", "27(m+1)", "3(9m+3)", "9m(3+1)"],
    "answer": "9(3m+1)"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "topic": "GCF",
    "question": "Factor: 20x^2y - 30xy",
    "choices": ["10xy(2x-3)", "20xy(x-3)", "5xy(4x-6)", "10x(2xy-3y)"],
    "answer": "10xy(2x-3)"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "topic": "GCF",
    "question": "Factor: 7a^2 + 14a",
    "choices": ["7a(a+2)", "14a(a+1)", "7(a^2+2a)", "a(7a+14)"],
    "answer": "7a(a+2)"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "topic": "GCF",
    "question": "Factor: 18x^2 - 12x",
    "choices": ["6x(3x-2)", "18x(x-2)", "3x(6x-4)", "6(3x^2-2x)"],
    "answer": "6x(3x-2)"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "topic": "GCF",
    "question": "Factor: 11x^2 + 22x",
    "choices": ["11x(x+2)", "22x(x+1)", "11(x^2+2x)", "x(11x+22)"],
    "answer": "11x(x+2)"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "topic": "GCF",
    "question": "Factor: 32a - 16",
    "choices": ["16(2a-1)", "32(a-1)", "8(4a-2)", "16a(2-1)"],
    "answer": "16(2a-1)"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "topic": "GCF",
    "question": "Factor: 45x^3 + 15x",
    "choices": ["15x(3x^2+1)", "45x(x^2+1)", "15(3x^3+x)", "5x(9x^2+3)"],
    "answer": "15x(3x^2+1)"
  },


  {
    "id": 21,
    "topic": "Grouping",
    "question": "Factor: 2x^2 + 6x + 3x + 9",
    "choices": ["(2x+3)(x+3)", "(x+3)^2", "(2x+9)(x+1)", "(x+6)(x+3)"],
    "answer": "(2x+3)(x+3)"
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "topic": "Grouping",
    "question": "Factor: x^2 + 5x + 2x + 10",
    "choices": ["(x+5)(x+2)", "(x+7)(x+1)", "(x+10)(x+1)", "(x+2)^2"],
    "answer": "(x+5)(x+2)"
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "topic": "Grouping",
    "question": "Factor: 3x^2 + 12x + 2x + 8",
    "choices": ["(3x+2)(x+4)", "(x+4)(x+8)", "(3x+8)(x+1)", "(x+2)(3x+4)"],
    "answer": "(3x+2)(x+4)"
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "topic": "Grouping",
    "question": "Factor: 4x^2 + 8x + 3x + 6",
    "choices": ["(4x+3)(x+2)", "(x+2)(x+6)", "(4x+6)(x+1)", "(x+3)(4x+2)"],
    "answer": "(4x+3)(x+2)"
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "topic": "Grouping",
    "question": "Factor: x^2 + 4x + 3x + 12",
    "choices": ["(x+3)(x+4)", "(x+6)(x+2)", "(x+12)(x+1)", "(x+3)^2"],
    "answer": "(x+3)(x+4)"
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "topic": "Grouping",
    "question": "Factor: 5x^2 + 10x + 3x + 6",
    "choices": ["(5x+3)(x+2)", "(x+2)(x+6)", "(5x+6)(x+1)", "(x+3)(5x+2)"],
    "answer": "(5x+3)(x+2)"
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "topic": "Grouping",
    "question": "Factor: 6x^2 + 9x + 4x + 6",
    "choices": ["(3x+2)(2x+3)", "(x+3)(6x+2)", "(6x+4)(x+1)", "(2x+3)^2"],
    "answer": "(3x+2)(2x+3)"
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "topic": "Grouping",
    "question": "Factor: 2x^2 + 7x + 4x + 14",
    "choices": ["(2x+7)(x+2)", "(x+7)(2x+2)", "(2x+14)(x+1)", "(x+2)^2"],
    "answer": "(2x+7)(x+2)"
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "topic": "Grouping",
    "question": "Factor: 3x^2 + 6x + 5x + 10",
    "choices": ["(3x+5)(x+2)", "(x+2)(x+10)", "(3x+10)(x+1)", "(x+5)(3x+2)"],
    "answer": "(3x+5)(x+2)"
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "topic": "Grouping",
    "question": "Factor: 4x^2 + 4x + 5x + 5",
    "choices": ["(4x+5)(x+1)", "(x+1)(x+5)", "(4x+1)(x+5)", "(x+4)(x+5)"],
    "answer": "(4x+5)(x+1)"
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "topic": "Grouping",
    "question": "Factor: 7x^2 + 14x + x + 2",
    "choices": ["(7x+1)(x+2)", "(x+2)(x+7)", "(7x+2)(x+1)", "(x+1)(7x+2)"],
    "answer": "(7x+1)(x+2)"
  },
  {
    "id": 32,
    "topic": "Grouping",
    "question": "Factor: 9x^2 + 3x + 6x + 2",
    "choices": ["(3x+2)(3x+1)", "(x+2)(9x+1)", "(3x+1)(x+2)", "(9x+2)(x+1)"],
    "answer": "(3x+2)(3x+1)"
  },
  {
    "id": 33,
    "topic": "Grouping",
    "question": "Factor: 10x^2 + 20x + x + 2",
    "choices": ["(10x+1)(x+2)", "(x+2)(x+10)", "(10x+2)(x+1)", "(x+1)(10x+2)"],
    "answer": "(10x+1)(x+2)"
  },
  {
    "id": 34,
    "topic": "Grouping",
    "question": "Factor: 8x^2 + 16x + 3x + 6",
    "choices": ["(8x+3)(x+2)", "(x+2)(x+6)", "(8x+6)(x+1)", "(x+3)(8x+2)"],
    "answer": "(8x+3)(x+2)"
  },
  {
    "id": 35,
    "topic": "Grouping",
    "question": "Factor: 2x^2 + 9x + 4x + 18",
    "choices": ["(2x+9)(x+2)", "(x+2)(x+18)", "(2x+18)(x+1)", "(x+4)(2x+9)"],
    "answer": "(2x+9)(x+2)"
  },
  {
    "id": 36,
    "topic": "Grouping",
    "question": "Factor: 6x^2 + 3x + 4x + 2",
    "choices": ["(3x+2)(2x+1)", "(x+2)(6x+1)", "(2x+3)(x+1)", "(6x+2)(x+1)"],
    "answer": "(3x+2)(2x+1)"
  },
  {
    "id": 37,
    "topic": "Grouping",
    "question": "Factor: 5x^2 + 15x + 2x + 6",
    "choices": ["(5x+2)(x+3)", "(x+3)(x+6)", "(5x+6)(x+1)", "(x+2)(5x+3)"],
    "answer": "(5x+2)(x+3)"
  },
  {
    "id": 38,
    "topic": "Grouping",
    "question": "Factor: 12x^2 + 6x + 4x + 2",
    "choices": ["(6x+2)(2x+1)", "(x+2)(12x+1)", "(4x+2)(3x+1)", "(12x+2)(x+1)"],
    "answer": "(6x+2)(2x+1)"
  },
  {
    "id": 39,
    "topic": "Grouping",
    "question": "Factor: 7x^2 + 21x + 2x + 6",
    "choices": ["(7x+2)(x+3)", "(x+3)(x+7)", "(7x+6)(x+1)", "(x+2)(7x+3)"],
    "answer": "(7x+2)(x+3)"
  },
  {
    "id": 40,
    "topic": "Grouping",
    "question": "Factor: 4x^2 + 12x + x + 3",
    "choices": ["(4x+1)(x+3)", "(x+3)(x+4)", "(4x+3)(x+1)", "(x+1)(4x+3)"],
    "answer": "(4x+1)(x+3)"
  },

  
  
  {
    "id": 41,
    "topic": "Difference of Squares",
    "question": "Factor: x^2 - 16",
    "choices": ["(x-4)(x+4)", "(x-8)(x+2)", "(x-2)(x+8)", "(x-16)(x+1)"],
    "answer": "(x-4)(x+4)"
  },
  {
    "id": 42,
    "topic": "Difference of Squares",
    "question": "Factor: 9y^2 - 25",
    "choices": ["(3y-5)(3y+5)", "(9y-5)(y+5)", "(y-5)(y+5)", "(3y-25)(y+1)"],
    "answer": "(3y-5)(3y+5)"
  },
  {
    "id": 43,
    "topic": "Difference of Squares",
    "question": "Factor: 4x^2 - 9",
    "choices": ["(2x-3)(2x+3)", "(4x-3)(x+3)", "(x-3)(x+3)", "(2x-9)(2x+1)"],
    "answer": "(2x-3)(2x+3)"
  },
  {
    "id": 44,
    "topic": "Difference of Squares",
    "question": "Factor: 16a^2 - 1",
    "choices": ["(4a-1)(4a+1)", "(16a-1)(a+1)", "(a-1)(a+1)", "(8a-1)(2a+1)"],
    "answer": "(4a-1)(4a+1)"
  },
  {
    "id": 45,
    "topic": "Difference of Squares",
    "question": "Factor: 25x^2 - 49",
    "choices": ["(5x-7)(5x+7)", "(25x-7)(x+7)", "(x-7)(x+7)", "(5x-49)(x+1)"],
    "answer": "(5x-7)(5x+7)"
  },
  {
    "id": 46,
    "topic": "Difference of Squares",
    "question": "Factor: 36m^2 - 4",
    "choices": ["(6m-2)(6m+2)", "(36m-2)(m+2)", "(3m-2)(3m+2)", "(18m-2)(2m+1)"],
    "answer": "(6m-2)(6m+2)"
  },
  {
    "id": 47,
    "topic": "Difference of Squares",
    "question": "Factor: x^2 - 81",
    "choices": ["(x-9)(x+9)", "(x-81)(x+1)", "(x-3)(x+27)", "(x-27)(x+3)"],
    "answer": "(x-9)(x+9)"
  },
  {
    "id": 48,
    "topic": "Difference of Squares",
    "question": "Factor: 49y^2 - 64",
    "choices": ["(7y-8)(7y+8)", "(49y-8)(y+8)", "(y-8)(y+8)", "(7y-64)(y+1)"],
    "answer": "(7y-8)(7y+8)"
  },
  {
    "id": 49,
    "topic": "Difference of Squares",
    "question": "Factor: 100x^2 - 1",
    "choices": ["(10x-1)(10x+1)", "(100x-1)(x+1)", "(x-1)(x+1)", "(20x-1)(5x+1)"],
    "answer": "(10x-1)(10x+1)"
  },
  {
    "id": 50,
    "topic": "Difference of Squares",
    "question": "Factor: 121a^2 - 9",
    "choices": ["(11a-3)(11a+3)", "(121a-3)(a+3)", "(a-3)(a+3)", "(11a-9)(a+1)"],
    "answer": "(11a-3)(11a+3)"
  },
  {
    "id": 51,
    "topic": "Difference of Squares",
    "question": "Factor: 64x^2 - 36",
    "choices": ["(8x-6)(8x+6)", "(4x-6)(4x+6)", "(16x-6)(4x+6)", "(8x-36)(x+1)"],
    "answer": "(8x-6)(8x+6)"
  },
  {
    "id": 52,
    "topic": "Difference of Squares",
    "question": "Factor: 144y^2 - 25",
    "choices": ["(12y-5)(12y+5)", "(144y-5)(y+5)", "(y-5)(y+5)", "(6y-5)(24y+5)"],
    "answer": "(12y-5)(12y+5)"
  },
  {
    "id": 53,
    "topic": "Difference of Squares",
    "question": "Factor: 1 - 16x^2",
    "choices": ["(1-4x)(1+4x)", "(1-16x)(1+x)", "(4-4x)(4+4x)", "(x-4)(x+4)"],
    "answer": "(1-4x)(1+4x)"
  },
  {
    "id": 54,
    "topic": "Difference of Squares",
    "question": "Factor: 81m^2 - 49",
    "choices": ["(9m-7)(9m+7)", "(81m-7)(m+7)", "(m-7)(m+7)", "(3m-7)(27m+7)"],
    "answer": "(9m-7)(9m+7)"
  },
  {
    "id": 55,
    "topic": "Difference of Squares",
    "question": "Factor: 9 - x^2",
    "choices": ["(3-x)(3+x)", "(9-x)(1+x)", "(x-3)(x+3)", "(x-9)(x+1)"],
    "answer": "(3-x)(3+x)"
  },
  {
    "id": 56,
    "topic": "Difference of Squares",
    "question": "Factor: 4 - 25y^2",
    "choices": ["(2-5y)(2+5y)", "(4-5y)(1+y)", "(5y-2)(5y+2)", "(y-5)(y+5)"],
    "answer": "(2-5y)(2+5y)"
  },
  {
    "id": 57,
    "topic": "Difference of Squares",
    "question": "Factor: x^2 - 1",
    "choices": ["(x-1)(x+1)", "(x-1)^2", "(x+1)^2", "(x-2)(x+2)"],
    "answer": "(x-1)(x+1)"
  },
  {
    "id": 58,
    "topic": "Difference of Squares",
    "question": "Factor: 36 - y^2",
    "choices": ["(6-y)(6+y)", "(y-6)(y+6)", "(36-y)(1+y)", "(y-18)(y+2)"],
    "answer": "(6-y)(6+y)"
  },
  {
    "id": 59,
    "topic": "Difference of Squares",
    "question": "Factor: 49 - 4x^2",
    "choices": ["(7-2x)(7+2x)", "(49-2x)(1+x)", "(2x-7)(2x+7)", "(x-2)(x+2)"],
    "answer": "(7-2x)(7+2x)"
  },
  {
    "id": 60,
    "topic": "Difference of Squares",
    "question": "Factor: 121 - 25a^2",
    "choices": ["(11-5a)(11+5a)", "(121-5a)(1+a)", "(5a-11)(5a+11)", "(a-5)(a+5)"],
    "answer": "(11-5a)(11+5a)"
  },

  
  {
    "id": 61,
    "topic": "Simple Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: x^2 + 7x + 10",
    "choices": ["(x+5)(x+2)", "(x+10)(x+1)", "(x+7)(x+3)", "(x+4)(x+5)"],
    "answer": "(x+5)(x+2)"
  },
  {
    "id": 62,
    "topic": "Simple Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: x^2 + 9x + 20",
    "choices": ["(x+5)(x+4)", "(x+10)(x+2)", "(x+20)(x+1)", "(x+6)(x+3)"],
    "answer": "(x+5)(x+4)"
  },
  {
    "id": 63,
    "topic": "Simple Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: x^2 + 8x + 12",
    "choices": ["(x+6)(x+2)", "(x+3)(x+4)", "(x+12)(x+1)", "(x+8)(x+1)"],
    "answer": "(x+6)(x+2)"
  },
  {
    "id": 64,
    "topic": "Simple Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: x^2 + 11x + 24",
    "choices": ["(x+3)(x+8)", "(x+6)(x+4)", "(x+12)(x+2)", "(x+1)(x+24)"],
    "answer": "(x+3)(x+8)"
  },
  {
    "id": 65,
    "topic": "Simple Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: x^2 + 10x + 21",
    "choices": ["(x+7)(x+3)", "(x+6)(x+4)", "(x+21)(x+1)", "(x+5)(x+5)"],
    "answer": "(x+7)(x+3)"
  },
  {
    "id": 66,
    "topic": "Simple Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: x^2 + 6x + 8",
    "choices": ["(x+4)(x+2)", "(x+8)(x+1)", "(x+6)(x+1)", "(x+3)(x+3)"],
    "answer": "(x+4)(x+2)"
  },
  {
    "id": 67,
    "topic": "Simple Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: x^2 + 13x + 36",
    "choices": ["(x+9)(x+4)", "(x+12)(x+3)", "(x+6)(x+6)", "(x+18)(x+2)"],
    "answer": "(x+9)(x+4)"
  },
  {
    "id": 68,
    "topic": "Simple Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: x^2 + 12x + 35",
    "choices": ["(x+7)(x+5)", "(x+10)(x+2)", "(x+12)(x+1)", "(x+6)(x+6)"],
    "answer": "(x+7)(x+5)"
  },
  {
    "id": 69,
    "topic": "Simple Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: x^2 + 5x + 6",
    "choices": ["(x+3)(x+2)", "(x+6)(x+1)", "(x+5)(x+1)", "(x+4)(x+2)"],
    "answer": "(x+3)(x+2)"
  },
  {
    "id": 70,
    "topic": "Simple Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: x^2 + 14x + 49",
    "choices": ["(x+7)^2", "(x+14)(x+1)", "(x+49)(x+1)", "(x+9)(x+5)"],
    "answer": "(x+7)^2"
  },
  {
    "id": 71,
    "topic": "Simple Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: x^2 - x - 12",
    "choices": ["(x-4)(x+3)", "(x-6)(x+2)", "(x-3)(x+4)", "(x-12)(x+1)"],
    "answer": "(x-4)(x+3)"
  },
  {
    "id": 72,
    "topic": "Simple Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: x^2 - 5x + 6",
    "choices": ["(x-2)(x-3)", "(x-6)(x+1)", "(x-1)(x-6)", "(x+2)(x-3)"],
    "answer": "(x-2)(x-3)"
  },
  {
    "id": 73,
    "topic": "Simple Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: x^2 - 7x + 10",
    "choices": ["(x-5)(x-2)", "(x-10)(x+1)", "(x-1)(x-10)", "(x+5)(x-2)"],
    "answer": "(x-5)(x-2)"
  },
  {
    "id": 74,
    "topic": "Simple Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: x^2 - 9x + 20",
    "choices": ["(x-5)(x-4)", "(x-10)(x+2)", "(x-1)(x-20)", "(x+4)(x-5)"],
    "answer": "(x-5)(x-4)"
  },
  {
    "id": 75,
    "topic": "Simple Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: x^2 - 11x + 24",
    "choices": ["(x-3)(x-8)", "(x-6)(x-4)", "(x-12)(x+2)", "(x-1)(x-24)"],
    "answer": "(x-3)(x-8)"
  },
  {
    "id": 76,
    "topic": "Simple Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: x^2 - 13x + 36",
    "choices": ["(x-9)(x-4)", "(x-6)(x-6)", "(x-12)(x-3)", "(x-18)(x+2)"],
    "answer": "(x-9)(x-4)"
  },
  {
    "id": 77,
    "topic": "Simple Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: x^2 - 4x - 12",
    "choices": ["(x-6)(x+2)", "(x-3)(x+4)", "(x+6)(x-2)", "(x-12)(x+1)"],
    "answer": "(x-6)(x+2)"
  },
  {
    "id": 78,
    "topic": "Simple Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: x^2 - 2x - 8",
    "choices": ["(x-4)(x+2)", "(x-8)(x+1)", "(x+4)(x-2)", "(x-1)(x+8)"],
    "answer": "(x-4)(x+2)"
  },
  {
    "id": 79,
    "topic": "Simple Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: x^2 + x - 12",
    "choices": ["(x+4)(x-3)", "(x+12)(x-1)", "(x+6)(x-2)", "(x-4)(x+3)"],
    "answer": "(x+4)(x-3)"
  },
  {
    "id": 80,
    "topic": "Simple Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: x^2 + 3x - 10",
    "choices": ["(x+5)(x-2)", "(x+10)(x-1)", "(x-5)(x+2)", "(x+1)(x-10)"],
    "answer": "(x+5)(x-2)"
  },
  
  {
    "id": 81,
    "topic": "General Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: 2x^2 + 7x + 3",
    "choices": ["(2x+1)(x+3)", "(x+1)(2x+3)", "(2x+3)(x+1)", "(x+3)(x+1)"],
    "answer": "(2x+1)(x+3)"
  },
  {
    "id": 82,
    "topic": "General Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: 3x^2 + 11x + 6",
    "choices": ["(3x+2)(x+3)", "(x+2)(3x+3)", "(3x+6)(x+1)", "(x+6)(3x+1)"],
    "answer": "(3x+2)(x+3)"
  },
  {
    "id": 83,
    "topic": "General Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: 4x^2 + 12x + 5",
    "choices": ["(4x+5)(x+1)", "(2x+5)(2x+1)", "(x+5)(4x+1)", "(4x+1)(x+5)"],
    "answer": "(4x+5)(x+1)"
  },
  {
    "id": 84,
    "topic": "General Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: 5x^2 + 14x + 8",
    "choices": ["(5x+4)(x+2)", "(x+4)(5x+2)", "(5x+8)(x+1)", "(x+8)(5x+1)"],
    "answer": "(5x+4)(x+2)"
  },
  {
    "id": 85,
    "topic": "General Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: 6x^2 + 13x + 6",
    "choices": ["(3x+2)(2x+3)", "(6x+2)(x+3)", "(2x+1)(3x+6)", "(x+2)(6x+3)"],
    "answer": "(3x+2)(2x+3)"
  },
  {
    "id": 86,
    "topic": "General Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: 2x^2 + 9x + 4",
    "choices": ["(2x+1)(x+4)", "(x+1)(2x+4)", "(2x+4)(x+1)", "(x+2)(2x+2)"],
    "answer": "(2x+1)(x+4)"
  },
  {
    "id": 87,
    "topic": "General Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: 7x^2 + 9x + 2",
    "choices": ["(7x+2)(x+1)", "(7x+1)(x+2)", "(x+7)(x+2)", "(x+1)(7x+2)"],
    "answer": "(7x+2)(x+1)"
  },
  {
    "id": 88,
    "topic": "General Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: 8x^2 + 10x + 3",
    "choices": ["(4x+3)(2x+1)", "(8x+3)(x+1)", "(2x+3)(4x+1)", "(x+3)(8x+1)"],
    "answer": "(4x+3)(2x+1)"
  },
  {
    "id": 89,
    "topic": "General Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: 9x^2 + 12x + 4",
    "choices": ["(3x+2)^2", "(9x+4)(x+1)", "(x+2)(9x+2)", "(3x+4)(3x+1)"],
    "answer": "(3x+2)^2"
  },
  {
    "id": 90,
    "topic": "General Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: 10x^2 + 9x + 2",
    "choices": ["(5x+2)(2x+1)", "(10x+1)(x+2)", "(2x+2)(5x+1)", "(x+2)(10x+1)"],
    "answer": "(5x+2)(2x+1)"
  },
  {
    "id": 91,
    "topic": "General Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: 4x^2 - x - 3",
    "choices": ["(4x+3)(x-1)", "(4x-3)(x+1)", "(x-3)(4x+1)", "(2x-3)(2x+1)"],
    "answer": "(4x+3)(x-1)"
  },
  {
    "id": 92,
    "topic": "General Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: 3x^2 - 5x - 2",
    "choices": ["(3x+1)(x-2)", "(3x-2)(x+1)", "(x-1)(3x+2)", "(x+2)(3x-1)"],
    "answer": "(3x+1)(x-2)"
  },
  {
    "id": 93,
    "topic": "General Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: 5x^2 - x - 6",
    "choices": ["(5x+4)(x-? )", "(5x-6)(x+1)", "(x-2)(5x+3)", "(5x+3)(x-2)"],
    "answer": "(5x+3)(x-2)"
  },
  {
    "id": 94,
    "topic": "General Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: 6x^2 - x - 2",
    "choices": ["(3x-2)(2x+1)", "(6x+1)(x-2)", "(2x-1)(3x+2)", "(x-2)(6x+1)"],
    "answer": "(3x-2)(2x+1)"
  },
  {
    "id": 95,
    "topic": "General Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: 8x^2 - 2x - 3",
    "choices": ["(4x-3)(2x+1)", "(8x-3)(x+1)", "(2x-3)(4x+1)", "(x-3)(8x+1)"],
    "answer": "(4x-3)(2x+1)"
  },
  {
    "id": 96,
    "topic": "General Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: 9x^2 - 6x + 1",
    "choices": ["(3x-1)^2", "(9x-1)(x-1)", "(3x+1)(3x-1)", "(x-1)(9x-1)"],
    "answer": "(3x-1)^2"
  },
  {
    "id": 97,
    "topic": "General Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: 4x^2 - 12x + 9",
    "choices": ["(2x-3)^2", "(4x-3)(x-3)", "(x-3)(4x-3)", "(2x+3)(2x-3)"],
    "answer": "(2x-3)^2"
  },
  {
    "id": 98,
    "topic": "General Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: 7x^2 - 14x + 7",
    "choices": ["7(x-1)^2", "(7x-7)(x-1)", "(x-7)(7x-1)", "(x-1)(7x-7)"],
    "answer": "7(x-1)^2"
  },
  {
    "id": 99,
    "topic": "General Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: 2x^2 - 3x - 5",
    "choices": ["(2x-5)(x+1)", "(x-5)(2x+1)", "(2x+5)(x-1)", "(x+5)(2x-1)"],
    "answer": "(2x-5)(x+1)"
  },
  {
    "id": 100,
    "topic": "General Trinomials",
    "question": "Factor: 3x^2 - 8x + 4",
    "choices": ["(3x-2)(x-2)", "(x-2)(3x-2)", "(3x+2)(x-2)", "(x+2)(3x-2)"],
    "answer": "(3x-2)(x-2)"
  },

 
  {
    "id": 101,
    "topic": "Completing the Square",
    "question": "Convert to vertex form: x^2 + 6x + 5",
    "choices": ["(x+3)^2 - 4", "(x+6)^2 + 5", "(x+3)^2 + 5", "(x+1)^2 + 4"],
    "answer": "(x+3)^2 - 4"
  },
  {
    "id": 102,
    "topic": "Completing the Square",
    "question": "Convert to vertex form: x^2 + 8x + 7",
    "choices": ["(x+4)^2 - 9", "(x+8)^2 + 7", "(x+4)^2 + 7", "(x+2)^2 + 3"],
    "answer": "(x+4)^2 - 9"
  },
  {
    "id": 103,
    "topic": "Completing the Square",
    "question": "Convert to vertex form: x^2 + 4x - 1",
    "choices": ["(x+2)^2 - 5", "(x+4)^2 - 1", "(x-2)^2 + 3", "(x+1)^2 - 2"],
    "answer": "(x+2)^2 - 5"
  },
  {
    "id": 104,
    "topic": "Completing the Square",
    "question": "Convert to vertex form: x^2 - 6x + 4",
    "choices": ["(x-3)^2 - 5", "(x-6)^2 + 4", "(x+3)^2 - 5", "(x-2)^2"],
    "answer": "(x-3)^2 - 5"
  },
  {
    "id": 105,
    "topic": "Completing the Square",
    "question": "Convert to vertex form: x^2 - 10x + 9",
    "choices": ["(x-5)^2 - 16", "(x-10)^2 + 9", "(x+5)^2 - 16", "(x-3)^2"],
    "answer": "(x-5)^2 - 16"
  },
  {
    "id": 106,
    "topic": "Completing the Square",
    "question": "Convert to vertex form: x^2 + 2x + 10",
    "choices": ["(x+1)^2 + 9", "(x+2)^2 + 10", "(x+1)^2 + 10", "(x-1)^2 + 11"],
    "answer": "(x+1)^2 + 9"
  },
  {
    "id": 107,
    "topic": "Completing the Square",
    "question": "Convert to vertex form: x^2 - 4x - 6",
    "choices": ["(x-2)^2 - 10", "(x-4)^2 - 6", "(x+2)^2 - 10", "(x-3)^2 - 3"],
    "answer": "(x-2)^2 - 10"
  },
  {
    "id": 108,
    "topic": "Completing the Square",
    "question": "Convert to vertex form: x^2 + 12x + 20",
    "choices": ["(x+6)^2 - 16", "(x+12)^2 + 20", "(x+6)^2 + 20", "(x+4)^2 + 4"],
    "answer": "(x+6)^2 - 16"
  },
  {
    "id": 109,
    "topic": "Completing the Square",
    "question": "Convert to vertex form: x^2 - 8x + 1",
    "choices": ["(x-4)^2 - 15", "(x-8)^2 + 1", "(x+4)^2 - 15", "(x-2)^2 - 3"],
    "answer": "(x-4)^2 - 15"
  },
  {
    "id": 110,
    "topic": "Completing the Square",
    "question": "Convert to vertex form: x^2 + x - 3",
    "choices": ["(x+0.5)^2 - 3.25", "(x+1)^2 - 4", "(x-0.5)^2 - 2.75", "(x+0.5)^2 - 2.75"],
    "answer": "(x+0.5)^2 - 3.25"
  },
  {
    "id": 111,
    "topic": "Completing the Square",
    "question": "Convert to vertex form: x^2 + 14x + 40",
    "choices": ["(x+7)^2 - 9", "(x+14)^2 + 40", "(x+7)^2 + 40", "(x+5)^2 + 15"],
    "answer": "(x+7)^2 - 9"
  },
  {
    "id": 112,
    "topic": "Completing the Square",
    "question": "Convert to vertex form: x^2 - 12x + 11",
    "choices": ["(x-6)^2 - 25", "(x-12)^2 + 11", "(x+6)^2 - 25", "(x-5)^2 - 14"],
    "answer": "(x-6)^2 - 25"
  },
  {
    "id": 113,
    "topic": "Completing the Square",
    "question": "Convert to vertex form: x^2 + 3x + 1",
    "choices": ["(x+1.5)^2 - 1.25", "(x+3)^2 + 1", "(x+1)^2", "(x-1.5)^2 + 1.25"],
    "answer": "(x+1.5)^2 - 1.25"
  },
  {
    "id": 114,
    "topic": "Completing the Square",
    "question": "Convert to vertex form: x^2 - x - 7",
    "choices": ["(x-0.5)^2 - 7.25", "(x-1)^2 - 6", "(x+0.5)^2 - 7.25", "(x-3)^2 + 2"],
    "answer": "(x-0.5)^2 - 7.25"
  },
  {
    "id": 115,
    "topic": "Completing the Square",
    "question": "Convert to vertex form: x^2 + 16x + 60",
    "choices": ["(x+8)^2 - 4", "(x+16)^2 + 60", "(x+8)^2 + 60", "(x+6)^2 + 24"],
    "answer": "(x+8)^2 - 4"
  },
  {
    "id": 116,
    "topic": "Completing the Square",
    "question": "Convert to vertex form: x^2 - 2x + 10",
    "choices": ["(x-1)^2 + 9", "(x-2)^2 + 10", "(x+1)^2 + 9", "(x-5)^2 - 15"],
    "answer": "(x-1)^2 + 9"
  },
  {
    "id": 117,
    "topic": "Completing the Square",
    "question": "Convert to vertex form: x^2 + 18x + 80",
    "choices": ["(x+9)^2 - 1", "(x+18)^2 + 80", "(x+9)^2 + 80", "(x+8)^2 + 16"],
    "answer": "(x+9)^2 - 1"
  },
  {
    "id": 118,
    "topic": "Completing the Square",
    "question": "Convert to vertex form: x^2 - 14x + 30",
    "choices": ["(x-7)^2 - 19", "(x-14)^2 + 30", "(x+7)^2 - 19", "(x-5)^2 + 5"],
    "answer": "(x-7)^2 - 19"
  },
  {
    "id": 119,
    "topic": "Completing the Square",
    "question": "Convert to vertex form: x^2 + 5x - 4",
    "choices": ["(x+2.5)^2 - 10.25", "(x+5)^2 - 4", "(x-2.5)^2 - 10.25", "(x+1)^2 - 5"],
    "answer": "(x+2.5)^2 - 10.25"
  },
  {
    "id": 120,
    "topic": "Completing the Square",
    "question": "Convert to vertex form: x^2 - 3x + 8",
    "choices": ["(x-1.5)^2 + 5.75", "(x-3)^2 + 8", "(x+1.5)^2 + 5.75", "(x-2)^2 + 4"],
    "answer": "(x-1.5)^2 + 5.75"
  },

  {
    "id": 121,
    "topic": "Solving Equations",
    "question": "Solve: x + 5 = 12",
    "choices": ["x = 7", "x = 17", "x = 5", "x = 12"],
    "answer": "x = 7"
  },
  {
    "id": 122,
    "topic": "Solving Equations",
    "question": "Solve: 3x = 15",
    "choices": ["x = 3", "x = 5", "x = 15", "x = 45"],
    "answer": "x = 5"
  },
  {
    "id": 123,
    "topic": "Solving Equations",
    "question": "Solve: 2x - 4 = 10",
    "choices": ["x = 3", "x = 7", "x = 14", "x = 8"],
    "answer": "x = 7"
  },
  {
    "id": 124,
    "topic": "Solving Equations",
    "question": "Solve: x/4 = 6",
    "choices": ["x = 10", "x = 24", "x = 6", "x = 2"],
    "answer": "x = 24"
  },
  {
    "id": 125,
    "topic": "Solving Equations",
    "question": "Solve: 5x + 3 = 18",
    "choices": ["x = 3", "x = 15", "x = 21", "x = 5"],
    "answer": "x = 3"
  },
  {
    "id": 126,
    "topic": "Solving Equations",
    "question": "Solve: 4x - 8 = 12",
    "choices": ["x = 1", "x = 4", "x = 5", "x = 20"],
    "answer": "x = 5"
  },
  {
    "id": 127,
    "topic": "Solving Equations",
    "question": "Solve: 6x = 42",
    "choices": ["x = 6", "x = 7", "x = 8", "x = 36"],
    "answer": "x = 7"
  },
  {
    "id": 128,
    "topic": "Solving Equations",
    "question": "Solve: x - 9 = -2",
    "choices": ["x = -11", "x = 11", "x = 7", "x = -7"],
    "answer": "x = 7"
  },
  {
    "id": 129,
    "topic": "Solving Equations",
    "question": "Solve: 7 + 2x = 21",
    "choices": ["x = 7", "x = 14", "x = 10", "x = 28"],
    "answer": "x = 7"
  },
  {
    "id": 130,
    "topic": "Solving Equations",
    "question": "Solve: 9x - 3 = 24",
    "choices": ["x = 3", "x = 9", "x = 27", "x = 21"],
    "answer": "x = 3"
  },
  {
    "id": 131,
    "topic": "Solving Equations",
    "question": "Solve: x/5 + 2 = 6",
    "choices": ["x = 20", "x = 10", "x = 30", "x = 8"],
    "answer": "x = 20"
  },
  {
    "id": 132,
    "topic": "Solving Equations",
    "question": "Solve: 8x + 4 = 36",
    "choices": ["x = 4", "x = 8", "x = 32", "x = 5"],
    "answer": "x = 4"
  },
  {
    "id": 133,
    "topic": "Solving Equations",
    "question": "Solve: 10 = x - 6",
    "choices": ["x = 4", "x = 16", "x = -16", "x = -4"],
    "answer": "x = 16"
  },
  {
    "id": 134,
    "topic": "Solving Equations",
    "question": "Solve: 12x = 3",
    "choices": ["x = 36", "x = 4", "x = 1/4", "x = 9"],
    "answer": "x = 1/4"
  },
  {
    "id": 135,
    "topic": "Solving Equations",
    "question": "Solve: 2(x + 3) = 14",
    "choices": ["x = 4", "x = 7", "x = 11", "x = 1"],
    "answer": "x = 4"
  },
  {
    "id": 136,
    "topic": "Solving Equations",
    "question": "Solve: 3(x - 2) = 9",
    "choices": ["x = 1", "x = 3", "x = 5", "x = 11"],
    "answer": "x = 5"
  },
  {
    "id": 137,
    "topic": "Solving Equations",
    "question": "Solve: 5x + 10 = 0",
    "choices": ["x = -10", "x = 2", "x = -2", "x = 0"],
    "answer": "x = -2"
  },
  {
    "id": 138,
    "topic": "Solving Equations",
    "question": "Solve: 4x/2 = 10",
    "choices": ["x = 2.5", "x = 5", "x = 10", "x = 20"],
    "answer": "x = 5"
  },
  {
    "id": 139,
    "topic": "Solving Equations",
    "question": "Solve: x + x = 18",
    "choices": ["x = 9", "x = 18", "x = 36", "x = 8"],
    "answer": "x = 9"
  },
  {
    "id": 140,
    "topic": "Solving Equations",
    "question": "Solve: 7x - 14 = 0",
    "choices": ["x = -2", "x = 2", "x = 14", "x = 0"],
    "answer": "x = 2"
  },

  {
    "id": 141,
    "topic": "Inequalities",
    "question": "Solve: x + 3 > 7",
    "choices": ["x > 4", "x < 4", "x > 10", "x < 10"],
    "answer": "x > 4"
  },
  {
    "id": 142,
    "topic": "Inequalities",
    "question": "Solve: 5x < 20",
    "choices": ["x < 4", "x > 4", "x < 100", "x > 100"],
    "answer": "x < 4"
  },
  {
    "id": 143,
    "topic": "Inequalities",
    "question": "Solve: x - 6 ≤ 2",
    "choices": ["x ≤ 8", "x ≥ 8", "x ≤ -4", "x ≥ -4"],
    "answer": "x ≤ 8"
  },
  {
    "id": 144,
    "topic": "Inequalities",
    "question": "Solve: 3x ≥ 15",
    "choices": ["x ≥ 5", "x ≤ 5", "x ≥ 45", "x ≤ 45"],
    "answer": "x ≥ 5"
  },
  {
    "id": 145,
    "topic": "Inequalities",
    "question": "Solve: -2x > 6",
    "choices": ["x < -3", "x > -3", "x < 3", "x > 3"],
    "answer": "x < -3"
  },
  {
    "id": 146,
    "topic": "Inequalities",
    "question": "Solve: x/4 ≥ 3",
    "choices": ["x ≥ 12", "x ≤ 12", "x ≥ 7", "x ≤ 7"],
    "answer": "x ≥ 12"
  },
  {
    "id": 147,
    "topic": "Inequalities",
    "question": "Solve: 7 - x < 10",
    "choices": ["x > -3", "x < -3", "x > 3", "x < 3"],
    "answer": "x > -3"
  },
  {
    "id": 148,
    "topic": "Inequalities",
    "question": "Solve: 2x + 1 ≤ 9",
    "choices": ["x ≤ 4", "x ≥ 4", "x ≤ 10", "x ≥ 10"],
    "answer": "x ≤ 4"
  },
  {
    "id": 149,
    "topic": "Inequalities",
    "question": "Solve: -3x ≤ 12",
    "choices": ["x ≥ -4", "x ≤ -4", "x ≥ 4", "x ≤ 4"],
    "answer": "x ≥ -4"
  },
  {
    "id": 150,
    "topic": "Inequalities",
    "question": "Solve: 4 < x + 2 < 10",
    "choices": ["2 < x < 8", "4 < x < 10", "6 < x < 12", "2 < x < 12"],
    "answer": "2 < x < 8"
  },
  {
    "id": 151,
    "topic": "Inequalities",
    "question": "Solve: -1 < x - 3 < 5",
    "choices": ["2 < x < 8", "-4 < x < 2", "-1 < x < 5", "3 < x < 9"],
    "answer": "2 < x < 8"
  },
  {
    "id": 152,
    "topic": "Inequalities",
    "question": "Solve: 0 ≤ 2x < 8",
    "choices": ["0 ≤ x < 4", "0 < x ≤ 4", "-4 ≤ x < 4", "x ≥ 4"],
    "answer": "0 ≤ x < 4"
  },
  {
    "id": 153,
    "topic": "Inequalities",
    "question": "Solve: -6 < -2x ≤ 4",
    "choices": ["-2 ≤ x < 3", "-3 < x ≤ 2", "2 ≤ x < -3", "-3 ≤ x < 2"],
    "answer": "-2 ≤ x < 3"
  },
  {
    "id": 154,
    "topic": "Inequalities",
    "question": "Solve: 1 < x/2 ≤ 5",
    "choices": ["2 < x ≤ 10", "1 < x ≤ 5", "2 ≤ x < 10", "x ≤ 2"],
    "answer": "2 < x ≤ 10"
  },
  {
    "id": 155,
    "topic": "Inequalities",
    "question": "Solve: -4 ≤ x + 1 < 6",
    "choices": ["-5 ≤ x < 5", "-3 ≤ x < 7", "-4 ≤ x < 6", "-5 < x ≤ 5"],
    "answer": "-5 ≤ x < 5"
  },
  {
    "id": 156,
    "topic": "Inequalities",
    "question": "Solve: 3x - 3 > 6",
    "choices": ["x > 3", "x < 3", "x > 9", "x < 9"],
    "answer": "x > 3"
  },
  {
    "id": 157,
    "topic": "Inequalities",
    "question": "Solve: -5x < -15",
    "choices": ["x > 3", "x < 3", "x > -3", "x < -3"],
    "answer": "x > 3"
  },
  {
    "id": 158,
    "topic": "Inequalities",
    "question": "Solve: x - 4 ≥ -1",
    "choices": ["x ≥ 3", "x ≤ 3", "x ≥ -5", "x ≤ -5"],
    "answer": "x ≥ 3"
  },
  {
    "id": 159,
    "topic": "Inequalities",
    "question": "Solve: 2 ≤ x + 5 ≤ 9",
    "choices": ["-3 ≤ x ≤ 4", "2 ≤ x ≤ 9", "-5 ≤ x ≤ 2", "3 ≤ x ≤ 14"],
    "answer": "-3 ≤ x ≤ 4"
  },
  {
    "id": 160,
    "topic": "Inequalities",
    "question": "Solve: -10 < 2x < 6",
    "choices": ["-5 < x < 3", "-10 < x < 6", "-5 ≤ x ≤ 3", "x > 3"],
    "answer": "-5 < x < 3"
  },
  [
  {
    "id": 161,
    "topic": "Fast Facts",
    "question": "Using the 9s finger trick, what is 9 × 3?",
    "choices": ["18", "21", "27", "36"],
    "answer": "27"
  },
  {
    "id": 162,
    "topic": "Fast Facts",
    "question": "Using the 9s finger trick, what is 9 × 7?",
    "choices": ["54", "56", "63", "72"],
    "answer": "63"
  },
  {
    "id": 163,
    "topic": "Fast Facts",
    "question": "Using the 9s finger trick, what is 9 × 4?",
    "choices": ["32", "34", "36", "40"],
    "answer": "36"
  },
  {
    "id": 164,
    "topic": "Fast Facts",
    "question": "Using the 9s finger trick, what is 9 × 8?",
    "choices": ["64", "70", "72", "80"],
    "answer": "72"
  },
  {
    "id": 165,
    "topic": "Fast Facts",
    "question": "Using the 9s finger trick, what is 9 × 6?",
    "choices": ["48", "52", "54", "56"],
    "answer": "54"
  },
  {
    "id": 166,
    "topic": "Fast Facts",
    "question": "Using the 9s finger trick, what is 9 × 9?",
    "choices": ["72", "80", "81", "90"],
    "answer": "81"
  },
  {
    "id": 167,
    "topic": "Fast Facts",
    "question": "Using the 11s trick, what is 23 × 11?",
    "choices": ["243", "253", "263", "273"],
    "answer": "253"
  },
  {
    "id": 168,
    "topic": "Fast Facts",
    "question": "Using the 11s trick, what is 34 × 11?",
    "choices": ["374", "344", "384", "394"],
    "answer": "374"
  },
  {
    "id": 169,
    "topic": "Fast Facts",
    "question": "Using the 11s trick, what is 45 × 11?",
    "choices": ["455", "495", "505", "515"],
    "answer": "495"
  },
  {
    "id": 170,
    "topic": "Fast Facts",
    "question": "Using the 11s trick, what is 62 × 11?",
    "choices": ["672", "682", "692", "702"],
    "answer": "682"
  },
  {
    "id": 171,
    "topic": "Fast Facts",
    "question": "Using the 11s trick, what is 57 × 11?",
    "choices": ["617", "627", "637", "647"],
    "answer": "627"
  },
  {
    "id": 172,
    "topic": "Fast Facts",
    "question": "Using the 11s trick, what is 81 × 11?",
    "choices": ["881", "891", "901", "911"],
    "answer": "891"
  },
  {
    "id": 173,
    "topic": "Fast Facts",
    "question": "What is 9 × 5?",
    "choices": ["40", "45", "50", "55"],
    "answer": "45"
  },
  {
    "id": 174,
    "topic": "Fast Facts",
    "question": "What is 9 × 2?",
    "choices": ["16", "17", "18", "19"],
    "answer": "18"
  },
  {
    "id": 175,
    "topic": "Fast Facts",
    "question": "What is 11 × 6?",
    "choices": ["60", "66", "72", "76"],
    "answer": "66"
  },
  {
    "id": 176,
    "topic": "Fast Facts",
    "question": "What is 11 × 9?",
    "choices": ["88", "90", "99", "109"],
    "answer": "99"
  },
  {
    "id": 177,
    "topic": "Fast Facts",
    "question": "Using mental math, what is 9 × 10?",
    "choices": ["81", "90", "99", "100"],
    "answer": "90"
  },
  {
    "id": 178,
    "topic": "Fast Facts",
    "question": "Using mental math, what is 11 × 8?",
    "choices": ["77", "88", "96", "108"],
    "answer": "88"
  },
  {
    "id": 179,
    "topic": "Fast Facts",
    "question": "What is 9 × 1?",
    "choices": ["0", "1", "9", "10"],
    "answer": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": 180,
    "topic": "Fast Facts",
    "question": "What is 11 × 11?",
    "choices": ["110", "111", "121", "131"],
    "answer": "121"
  }
]






]
